Georgios Oikonomitsios

oikonomitsios.george@outlook.com | (+974) 6652-5070 | <u>george.oikonomitsios.com</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/georgeoikonomitsios</u> 880 street, zone 26, building 34, Doha, Qatar

SUMMARY

A self-motivated, adaptable, and continuously learning Cabin Services Director with over 10 years in the Aviation Industry in Qatar, looking to transition back to the education industry utilizing all knowledge, communication and management skills acquired throughout the years.

EXPERIENCE

LAFERIENCE	
QATAR AIRWAYS	DOHA, QATAR
Cabin Services Director	09/2018 - Current
 Responsible for the optimal operation of each flight, ensuring the safety and wellbeing for all passengers and crew. 	
 Responsible for documenting and reporting all flight details, security, and medical incidents with HQ. Promoting a healthy working environment motivating each cabin crew to flourish, grow and continuously improve their performance and service towards our customers. Regularly selected to lead high profile VIP flights for unique events. 	
Cabin Senior	
 Continuously improved the performance and competitiveness of the cabin crew team and the service they provided to our customers through leadership and management of cabin crew. Ranked 2nd scoring 98% in the Cabin Senior selection assessment among all eligible candidates. 	09/2015 - 09/2018
F1 Premium Cabin Crew	,
 Provided an outstanding customer service, by creating an environment that impressed our Premium Class customers, through service and by recognizing their individual needs. 	
F2 Economy Cabin Crew	
 Provided a consistent and outstanding customer service to all our customers to increase their loyalty and establish the reputation and image of Cabin Crew as a distinct competitive advantage for Qatar Airways. 	05/2013 – 09/2015
NEW AGE ENGLISH	09/2011 - 05/2013
English Language Teacher	
Worked with children aged 5 to 12 years old, teaching English as a language	

02/2011 - 07/2011

EDUCATION

NATIONAL AND KAPODISTRIAN UNIVERSITY OF ATHENS BSc Geology Expected 2024

Studied the subterranean environment of Greece, geological techniques, and phenomena of earth.

CERTIFICATIONS

-	edX & Harvard University CS50x - CS50's Introduction to Computer Science	Ongoing
	Udemy The Complete 2021 Web Development Bootcamp	0 0
-		Ongoing
•	Udemy Python GUI Programming Using PyQt5	07/2020
•	Udemy Linux Administration Bootcamp: Go from Beginner to Advanced	04/2020
-	Udemy Python GUI Programming Using Tkinter and SQLite3	02/2020
•	Qatar Airways Senior Leadership Excellence	08/2018
•	Qatar Airways Cultural and Emotional Intelligence	11/2017
•	Pan-Hellenic Seminar on Children with Learning Difficulties	05/2011

SKILLS

Operating Systems: Windows, Mac OS X, Linux

Office: Office 365, Outlook, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, SharePoint

Communication Platforms: Zoom, Microsoft Teams, Google Hangouts, Slack **Programming Languages:** Python, C#, Unity, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, jQuery, SQL

LANGUAGES

Greek – Proficient; English – Proficient (Proficiency, Cambridge University); German – Intermediate (Grundstufe, Goethe
Institute)
institute)